[
{
    "question":"Which game during the 2014 world cup was the most one sided",
    "correct":"0",
    "a1":"Brazil Vs Germany",
    "a2":"Germany vs Argentina",
    "a3":"Argentina vs Nthrland",
    "a4":"Ntherland vs Brazil"
},
  {
    "question":"What is the name of Aang's mentor",
    "correct":"2",
    "a1":"Tenzin",
    "a2":"Zhang",
    "a3":"Gyatzo",
    "a4":"Rohan"
  },
  {
    "question":"Who was the voice actor for Fire Lord Ozai",
    "correct":"1",
    "a1":"Dante Basco",
    "a2":"Mark Hamil",
    "a3":"Mako",
    "a4":"Jack Desena"
  },
  {
    "question":"What is the name of Daniel's teacher in the original Karate Kid?",
    "correct":"2",
    "a1":"Mizagi",
    "a2":"Misagi",
    "a3":"Miyagi",
    "a4":"Mitagi"
  },
  {
    "question":"What is the name of Daniels rival in the original Karate Kid",
    "correct":"3",
    "a1":"Jeremy",
    "a2":"Luke",
    "a3":"Blake",
    "a4":"Johnny"
  },
  {
    "question":"What is the name of students that Michael Scott promised to give college tuition to",
    "correct":"0",
    "a1":"Scotts Tots",
    "a2":"Scotts Scholars",
    "a3":"Michaels Ballers",
    "a4":"Michaels Students"
  },
  {
    "question":"What is the name of the person most responsible for prohibition in the 1920's",
    "correct":"1",
    "a1":"Scott Douglass",
    "a2":"Wayne Wheeler",
    "a3":"Fredrick Douglass",
    "a4":"President Hoover"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the secret society that uncle Iroh is in?",
    "correct": "2",
    "a1": "The secret society",
    "a2": "Red roses",
    "a3": "White Lotus",
    "a4": "Red Lotus"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the planned release date for Overwatch 2?",
    "correct": "3",
    "a1": "2021",
    "a2": "2022",
    "a3": "2023",
    "a4": "Never"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the best way to kill somebody in valorant?",
    "correct": "2",
    "a1": "be patient",
    "a2": "use abilities",
    "a3": "Run and Gun",
    "a4": "Stand still and shoot"
  }
]